{
  "quiz": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "The portrait that appears on the two hundred naira note is that of?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Abubakar Tafawa Balewa",
        "B": "Ahmadu Bello",
        "C": "Alvan Ikoku",
        "D": "Nnamdi Azikiwe",
        "E": "Obafemi Awolowo"
      },
      "correct": "A"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "The coctus spectabilis on the Nigeria Coat of Arms represents?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Agriculture",
        "B": "Beauty",
        "C": "Culture",
        "D": "Oil",
        "E": "Wealth"
      },
      "correct": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Nigeria is divided into how many geopolitical zones?",
      "options": {
        "A": "3",
        "B": "6",
        "C": "12",
        "D": "36",
        "E": "37"
      },
      "correct": "B"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Which of the following can lead to drug abuse?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Following doctor's prescription",
        "B": "Good family background",
        "C": "Obeying the laws",
        "D": "Peer group influence",
        "E": "Resistance to temptation"
      },
      "correct": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Which of the following ethnic groups occupy the South-Eastern part of Nigeria?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Esan",
        "B": "Igbo",
        "C": "Ijaw",
        "D": "Tiv",
        "E": "Yoruba"
      },
      "correct": "B"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "The nuclear family consists of?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Father, mother and children",
        "B": "Father, mother and grandparent",
        "C": "Mother, brother and cousin",
        "D": "Niece, children and parent",
        "E": "Uncle, aunty and nephew"
      },
      "correct": "A"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Nigeria became a republic in?",
      "options": {
        "A": "1960",
        "B": "1953",
        "C": "1966",
        "D": "1967",
        "E": "1970"
      },
      "correct": "A"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "The Senate in Nigeria consists of how many members?",
      "options": {
        "A": "36",
        "B": "37",
        "C": "109",
        "D": "360",
        "E": "774"
      },
      "correct": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "The horses on the Nigeria Coat of Arms symbolize?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Authority",
        "B": "Democracy",
        "C": "Dignity",
        "D": "Peace",
        "E": "Unity"
      },
      "correct": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "\"To be faithful, loyal and honest\" is a phrase in the Nigeria national?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Anthem",
        "B": "Constitution",
        "C": "Motto",
        "D": "Pledge",
        "E": "Prayer"
      },
      "correct": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "Community relationship can be promoted by?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Backbiting",
        "B": "Malice",
        "C": "Marriage",
        "D": "Helping others",
        "E": "Selfishness"
      },
      "correct": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "Values are maintained in the society to promote?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Arrogance",
        "B": "Dispute",
        "C": "Modernization",
        "D": "Orderliness",
        "E": "Selfishness"
      },
      "correct": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "Personal security can be enhanced by?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Avoiding mad people",
        "B": "Interacting with strangers",
        "C": "Playing with chemicals",
        "D": "Tampering with electric wires",
        "E": "Using fake drugs"
      },
      "correct": "A"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "Which of the following security outfits is community based?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Army",
        "B": "Civil Defence Corps",
        "C": "Immigration",
        "D": "Police",
        "E": "Vigilante"
      },
      "correct": "E"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "The following items can be found in a first aid box except?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Antiseptic",
        "B": "Bandage",
        "C": "Plaster",
        "D": "Scissors",
        "E": "Syringe"
      },
      "correct": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "Mary is taller than?",
      "options": {
        "A": "I",
        "B": "Me",
        "C": "Us",
        "D": "She",
        "E": "Them"
      },
      "correct": "B"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "Kikelomo said buses over there belonged to her uncle. Which word completes the sentence?",
      "options": {
        "A": "That",
        "B": "These",
        "C": "This",
        "D": "Those",
        "E": "Which"
      },
      "correct": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "Which of the following is not a communication device?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Cell phone",
        "B": "Radio",
        "C": "Television",
        "D": "Typewriter",
        "E": "Walkie-talkie"
      },
      "correct": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "Social studies deals with man and his?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Activities",
        "B": "Biography",
        "C": "Environment",
        "D": "Lineage",
        "E": "Religion"
      },
      "correct": "A"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "The existence of various cultures within a society is cultural?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Comparison",
        "B": "Discrimination",
        "C": "Diversity",
        "D": "Superiority",
        "E": "Unification"
      },
      "correct": "C"
    }
  ]
}
